[music]
>> Want to clear [singing] a bottle or
cabinet.
>> [music]
>> Want to stay home, not even drink. Want
to get out of [singing] my own head.
Want to lay down over the sink. [music]
I want to cry every [singing] tear I
got. Put on a dress, be a stranger's
dream. Light up this heart of mine. Want
to wear it on my sleeve.
I kind of want to hate you, but I want
to love you, too. I want to hold you
close [singing] and let you go, find
someone new. [music] And now I wish it
wasn't, but [singing]
my mind's made up in two. What's killing
me the most is knowing two things can be
[music] true.
Want to throw away your vanity. [music]
Want to wear it to sleep tonight. Want
to wipe our slate [music and singing]
clean. Want to pick this thing apart.
Where we left off, want to [music] block
your number, take one last time, make it
[singing] another.
Wish I was one [music] or the other.
I kind of want to hate you, but I want
to love you, too. I want to hold you
close and [music and singing] let you
go, find someone new. And now I wish it
wasn't, but my mind's made up in two.
[music] What's killing me the most is
knowing [singing]
two things can be true.
>> [music]
[music]
>> If it's [singing] black, it's white. If
it's wrong, it's right. Soon [singing]
as I pick one, [music] I switch sides.
I kind of want to hate you, but I want
to I you, too. I want to you close and
[music] let you go find someone
[singing] new. I know this wasn't
but
my mind's made up and two. What's
killing me the most is knowing
[music and singing]
two things can be true.
Two [singing] things can be true.
[music]
>> [singing]
[singing]
[music]
>> Two things can be true.
But I want to love you [singing] too. I
want to hold you close and let [music]
you go find someone new. I know this
[singing] wasn't but
my mind's made up and two. What's
killing me the most is knowing
>> [singing and music]
>> two things can be true.
Want to throw [music] away your panties.
Want to wear to sleep tonight. Want to
wipe our slate [music] clean. Want to
pick this thing apart. Where we left
off. Want to block [music and singing]
your number. Take one last time make it
another.
Wish I was one or the other.
>> [music and singing]
>> I kind of want to hate you but I want to
love you too. [singing]
I want to hold you close and let you go
find [music] someone new. I know this
wasn't [singing] but
my mind's made up and two. What's
killing me the most is
[singing and music] knowing two things
can be true.
>> [singing and music]
>> If it's black, it's white. If it's
wrong, it's right. Soon as I
pick one